Emilia Cortegozo

Cordoba, Córdoba, Argentina



Mecortegozo@Gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/emiliacortegozo

Summary

Hi! I'm Emilia, a web development enthusiast and a graduate in psychology This gave me knowledge and experience thanks to which I enjoy working in groups and with groups, that's why I like to think that I have very good communication skills which I consider key to solve problems, and or find other ways. I was recently selected for the "Grow with Google for Women in STEM" Program (Science, Technology, Engineering and Mathematics) to continue my professional preparation in IT.

Experience



Psicología

Autónomo

Dec 2018 - Feb 2022 (3 years 3 months)

docente adscripto

Universidad Nacional de Córdoba May 2019 - 2022 (3 years) Facultad de Psicología

Education



Universidad Nacional de Córdoba

Bachelor's degree, Psychology

Google Cloud Training

Cloud Learning Workshop LATAM with Women in STEM Fall 2022 Sep 2022 - Present

Henry

Full stack developer Jan 2022 - 2022

Yale School of Public Health

Addiction treatment: clinical skills for healthcare providers, Asesoramiento psicológico 2020 - 2020

University of Buenos Aires

Posgrado, Psicoanálisis y psicoterapia 2020 - 2021

Licenses & Certifications

- **English Certificate C1 Advanced** EF Standard English Test (EF SET)
- Cloud Computing Google Activate
 ASS Y6N 9QF
- Desarrollo de Apps moviles Google Actívate
 AQ3 B32 AD9
- Google Cloud Fundamentals: Core Infrastructure Google Cloud Training Online https://coursera.org/verify/AK4F3USGEFXA
- Google Cloud Essential Cloud Infrastructure: Foundation Google Cloud Training Online https://coursera.org/verify/UBPKLWH68QV4
- Essential Cloud Infrastructure: Core Services Google Cloud Training Online
- Elastic Google Cloud Infrastructure: Scaling and Automation Google Cloud Training Online
- Reliable Google Cloud Infrastructure: Design and Process Google Cloud Training Online
- Especialización de Google Cloud Architecting with Google Compute Engine. -Google Cloud Training Online
- Create and Manage Cloud Resources Google Cloud Skills Boost 3203640

Skills

React.is • Google Cloud Platform (GCP) • English • JavaScript • Node.js • Research • Training